<ScrollView
    xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="match_parent"
    android:padding="16dp">

    <TextView
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:text="Terms and Conditions\n\nWelcome to Smart Screen Guard! By using this app, you agree to the following terms and conditions. Please read them carefully.\n\n1. App Purpose\nSmart Screen Guard is designed to help users manage and reduce screen time, promote digital well-being, and prevent excessive app usage. The app may include features such as usage tracking, app blocking, screen locking, and keyword filtering.\n\n2. Permissions\nThe app requires access to system-level permissions including Usage Access, Accessibility Service, and Overlay Permission. These are essential for enabling core functionality like detecting app usage, blocking specific apps, or locking the device screen.\n\n3. Data Collection\nSmart Screen Guard does not collect personal data from users. All usage statistics and preferences are stored locally on the user's device. We do not share, sell, or transmit any user data to third parties.\n\n4. Accessibility Service\nOur app uses Accessibility Services to monitor and control app behavior for the purpose of enforcing user-set restrictions. This service is never used to collect or store personal information.\n\n5. User Responsibility\nYou are responsible for the settings and restrictions applied through Smart Screen Guard. We are not liable for any unintended device lockouts or data loss due to configuration choices made by the user.\n\n6. Changes to the App\nFeatures and functionality may change over time as we update the app. We reserve the right to add, modify, or remove any part of the app at any time without notice.\n\n7. Limitation of Liability\nSmart Screen Guard is provided “as is” without warranty of any kind. We are not liable for any damages or losses that may result from using this app.\n\n8. Contact\nFor questions or feedback, you may contact us via the support section of the app.\n\nBy continuing to use Smart Screen Guard, you acknowledge that you have read and understood these terms and agree to comply with them."
        android:textSize="16sp"
        android:lineSpacingExtra="4dp" />
</ScrollView>
